Pinelands Folklife Project collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Field documentation arranged by fieldworker, Field photography descriptions are copied directly from B and C logs via Optical Character Recognition, so errors and abbreviations exist.
  - Malachi O'Connor
    - Field recordings on reel-to-reel audio tape
      - Interview with Armand Carney and Pamela Carney, New Gretna, New Jersey, part 4, October 22, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23935; Malachi O'Connor; PFP-83-RMO-013; RXA 6022; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch)
      - Interview with Stephen Lee Jr. and his sons, Stephen III and Abbot, New Jersey, part 1, November 12, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23936; Malachi O'Connor; PFP-83-RMO-014; RXA 6023; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch); Mary Hufford
        G-Speedwell; 27GT
      - Interview with Stephen Lee Jr. and his sons, Stephen III and Abbot, New Jersey, part 2, November 12, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23937; Malachi O'Connor; PFP-83-RMO-015; RXA 6024; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch); Mary Hufford
      - Interview with Stephen Lee Jr. and his sons, Stephen III and Abbot, New Jersey, part 3, November 12, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23938; Malachi O'Connor; PFP-83-RMO-016; RXA 6025; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch); Mary Hufford
      - Interview with Stephen Lee Jr. and his sons, Stephen III and Abbot, New Jersey, part 4, November 12, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23939; Malachi O'Connor; PFP-83-RMO-017; RXA 6026; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch); Mary Hufford
      - Interview with Stephen Lee Jr. and his sons, Stephen III and Abbot, New Jersey, part 5, November 12, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23940; Malachi O'Connor; PFP-83-RMO-018; RXA 6027; 1 audiotape reel (5 inch); Mary Hufford
      - Interview with George Heinrichs, New Gretna, New Jersey, part 1, November 18, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23941; Malachi O'Connor; PFP-83-RMO-019; RXA 6028; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch)
      - Interview with George Heinrichs and Catherine Heinrichs, New Gretna, New Jersey, part 1, November 18, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23942; Malachi O'Connor; PFP-83-RMO-020; RXA 6029; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch)
      - Interview with George Heinrichs and Catherine Heinrichs, New Gretna, New Jersey, part 2, November 18, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23943; Malachi O'Connor; PFP-83-RMO-021; RXA 6030; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch)
      - Interview with George Heinrichs and Catherine Heinrichs, New Gretna, New Jersey, part 3, November 18, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23944; Malachi O'Connor; PFP-83-RMO-022; RXA 6031; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch)
      - Interview with Cliff Frazee and tour of his tree farm and swamp, New Jersey, October 7, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23945; Malachi O'Connor; PFP-83-RMO-023; RXA 6032; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch); Mary Hufford
        G-Forked River: 48GT
      - Interview with Cliff Frazee and tour of his tree farm and swamp, New Jersey, October 7, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23946; Malachi O'Connor; PFP-83-RMO-024; RXA 6033; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch); Mary Hufford
      - Interview with Cliff Frazee and tour of his tree farm and swamp, New Jersey, October 7, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23947; Malachi O'Connor; PFP-83-RMO-025; RXA 6034; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch); Mary Hufford
      - Interview with Cliff Frazee and tour of his tree farm and swamp, New Jersey, October 7, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23948; Malachi O'Connor; PFP-83-RMO-026; RXA 6035; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch); Mary Hufford
    - Final report
      - Final report, Malachi O'Connor; 7 manuscript pages (8.5 x 14 inch or smaller) (Box-folder 16/144)
  - Gerald E. Parsons
    - Memos
      - Memos, Gerald E. Parsons; 30 manuscript pages (8.5 x 14 inch or smaller) (Box-folder 16/145)
    - Field recordings on audiocassette
      - A log (audiocassette log), Gerald E. Parsons; 12 manuscript pages (8.5 x 14 inch or smaller) (Box-folder 16/146)
      - Interview with Albert Reeves and Frank Astemborski, Mauricetown, New Jersey, part 1, August 11, 1984, AFC 1991/023: AFS 24074; Gerald E. Parsons; PFP-84-AGP-001; RYA 4903; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
      - Interview with Albert Reeves and Frank Astemborski, Mauricetown, New Jersey, part 2, August 11, 1984, AFC 1991/023: AFS 24075; Gerald E. Parsons; PFP-84-AGP-002; RYA 4904; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
      - Interview with Albert Reeves and Frank Astemborski, Mauricetown, New Jersey, part 3 (starts at 4:13), August 11, 1984, AFC 1991/023: AFS 24076; Gerald E. Parsons; PFP-84-AGP-003; RYA 4905; 1 audiocassette (60 minute); Carl Fleischhauer
    - Field photography on color slide film
      - C log (color photo log), July 8, 1999, Gerald E. Parsons; 4 manuscript pages (8.5 x 14 inch or smaller); Reprinted from askSam database 07/08/1999 (Box-folder 16/147)
      - Preliminary fieldwork for railbirding, New Jersey, 1984, AFC 1991/023: CGP84-001; Gerald E. Parsons; PFP-84-CGP-001; 17 color film transparencies (35mm slide); Frank Astemborski; Not in log
      - Preliminary fieldwork for railbirding, New Jersey, 1984, AFC 1991/023: CGP84-002; Gerald E. Parsons; PFP-84-CGP-002; 14 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
      - Railbirding on Maurice River, New Jersey, October 24, 1984, AFC 1991/023: CGP84-003; Gerald E. Parsons; PFP-84-CGP-003; 10 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
      - Railbirding at Milton Weatherby's Meadow on Maurice River above Port Elizabeth, New Jersey, October 1984, AFC 1991/023: CGP84-004; Gerald E. Parsons; PFP-84-CGP-004; 16 color film transparencies (35mm slide); Not in log
      - Railbirding, possibly on the Patuxent River, Ann Arundel County, Maryland, September 1984, AFC 1991/023: CGP84-005; Gerald E. Parsons; PFP-84-CGP-005; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide); Not in log
    - Field recordings on reel-to-reel audio tape
      - R log (reel-to-reel log), Gerald E. Parsons; 119 manuscript pages (8.5 x 14 inch or smaller) (Box-folder 16/148)
      - Railbirding on the Patuxent with James P. Owings and Frank Astemborski, between 1983 and 1985, AFC 1991/023: AFS 24065; Gerald E. Parsons; PFP-84-RGP-001; RXA 6099; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch); Paula J. Johnson, Carl Fleischhauer
      - Railbirding on the Patuxent with James P. Owings and Frank Astemborski, between 1983 and 1985, AFC 1991/023: AFS 24066; Gerald E. Parsons; PFP-84-RGP-002; RXA 6100; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch); Paula J. Johnson, Carl Fleischhauer
      - Interview with Frank Astemborski, Washington, D.C., September 8, 1984, AFC 1991/023: AFS 24067; Gerald E. Parsons; PFP-84-RGP-003; RXA 6101; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch)
      - Interview with Albert Reeves, Frank Astemborski, and Jim Owings, Mauricetown, New Jersey, part 1, September 24, 1984, AFC 1991/023: AFS 24068; Gerald E. Parsons; PFP-84-RGP-004; RXA 6102; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch)
      - Interview with Albert Reeves, Frank Astemborski, and Jim Owings, Mauricetown, New Jersey, part 2, September 24, 1984, AFC 1991/023: AFS 24069; Gerald E. Parsons; PFP-84-RGP-006; RXA 6103; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch)
      - Interview with Albert Reeves, Frank Astemborski, and Jim Owings, Mauricetown, New Jersey, part 3, September 24, 1984, AFC 1991/023: AFS 24070; Gerald E. Parsons; PFP-84-RGP-007; RXA 6104; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch)
      - Interview with Kenneth Camp, Port Elizabeth, New Jersey, part 1, October 2, 1984, AFC 1991/023: AFS 24071; Gerald E. Parsons; PFP-84-RGP-008; RXA 6105; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch)
      - Sora rail hunting, Maurice River near Port Elizabeth, New Jersey, October 2, 1984, AFC 1991/023: AFS 24072; Gerald E. Parsons; PFP-84-RGP-009; RXA 6106; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch)
      - Interview with Kenneth Camp, Port Elizabeth, New Jersey, part 2, October 2, 1984, AFC 1991/023: AFS 24073; Gerald E. Parsons; PFP-84-RGP-010; RXA 6107; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch)
  - Nora Jane Rubinstein
    - Field notes
      - Field notes, Nora Jane Rubinstein; 30 manuscript pages (8.5 x 14 inch or smaller) (Box-folder 16/149)
    - Field recordings on audiocassette
      - A log (audiocassette log), Nora Jane Rubinstein; 50 manuscript pages (8.5 x 14 inch or smaller) (Box-folder 16/150)
      - Interview with Bill Thoms and Jean Thoms, Hammonton, New Jersey, September 16, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23968; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-ANR-001; RYA 4856; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
      - Woods walk with Jack Carvetto, Pearl Carvetto, and John Budd, Warren Grove, New Jersey, part 1, October 28, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23969; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-ANR-002; RYA 4857; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
      - Woods walk with Jack Carvetto, Pearl Carvetto, and John Budd, Warren Grove, New Jersey, part 2, October 28, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23970; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-ANR-003; RYA 4858; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
      - Woods walk with Jack Carvetto, Pearl Carvetto, and John Budd, Warren Grove, New Jersey, part 3, October 28, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23971; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-ANR-004; RYA 4859; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
      - Woods walk with Jack Carvetto, Pearl Carvetto, and John Budd, Warren Grove, New Jersey, part 4, October 28, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23972; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-ANR-005; RYA 4860; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
      - Interview with Elaine and John Schuck, Barnegat, New Jersey, part 1, November 2, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23973; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-ANR-006; RYA 4861; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
        G-Barnegat; 42GT
      - Interview with Elaine and John Schuck, Barnegat, New Jersey, part 2, November 2, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23974; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-ANR-007; RYA 4862; 1 audiocassette (90 minute)
      - Interview with Elaine and John Schuck, Barnegat, New Jersey, part 3, November 2, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23975; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-ANR-008; RYA 4863; 1 audiocassette (90 minute)
      - Interview with Elaine and John Schuck, Barnegat, New Jersey, part 4, November 2, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23976; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-ANR-009; RYA 4864; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
      - Interview with Jack Cervetto, New Jersey, part 1, November 5, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23977; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-ANR-010; RYA 4865; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
      - Interview with Jack Cervetto, New Jersey, part 2, November 5, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23978; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-ANR-011; RYA 4866; 1 audiocassette (90 minute)
      - Interview with Jack Cervetto, New Jersey, part 3, November 5, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23979; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-ANR-012; RYA 4867; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
      - Interview with Jack Cervetto, New Jersey, part 4, November 5, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23980; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-ANR-013; RYA 4868; 1 audiocassette (90 minute)
      - Interview with Jack Cervetto, New Jersey, part 5, November 5, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23981; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-ANR-014; RYA 4869; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
      - Interview with Jack Cervetto, New Jersey, part 6, November 5, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23982; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-ANR-015; RYA 4870; 1 audiocassette (90 minute)
      - Interview with Jack Cervetto, New Jersey, part 7, November 5, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23983; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-ANR-016; RYA 4871; 1 audiocassette (60 minute)
    - Field photography on black-and-white film
      - B log (black-and-white photo log), Nora Jane Rubinstein; 6 manuscript pages (8.5 x 14 inch or smaller) (Box-folder 16/151)
        See also Rubinstein, Nora--B/W contact sheets in Field Project Reference File in Reading Room
      - Woods walk with Jack Cervetto and John Budd; Benefit at Old Stone Store in Manahawkin, New Jersey; Halloween party at Warren Grove Firehouse, Warren Grove, New Jersey, October 28, 1983 to October 29, 1983, AFC 1991/023: 217302-06; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-BNR-217302-06; 30 black-and-white film negatives (35mm)
        G-Warren Grove; 56GT; Frames 0 & 1, Jack Cervetto and John Budd in Jack's 1941 Jeep; Frame 2, Woodpecker eaten tree; Frames 3, 4, 5, Indian Pipes; Frame 6, Sweet Fern -"woodjin' s enemy"; Frame 7 & 8, Jack and Pearl Cervetto; Frame 9, Blanchard House Frames 10, 11 & 12, View from Bear Swamp Hill; Frame 13 & 14, John Budd, Jack and Pearl Cervetto at Bear Swamp Hill; Frame 15, 16 & 17, Target practice; Frames 18 & 19, Pine Barrens Gentian; Frames 20 & 21, Pig at Beaver Dam Road House; Frame 22, Pine Barrens Gentian; Frames 23, 24 & 25, Ed Hazelton, Jack Cervetto and John Budd at Old Stone Store in G-Manahawkin; 56GT (left to right); Frames 26 & 27, Cervettos with friends; Frames 28 & 29, Halloween Party at G-Warren Grove; 56GT.
      - Warren Grove Firehouse Halloween party, Warren Grove, New Jersey, October 29, 1983, AFC 1991/023: 217302-07; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-BNR-217302-07; 38 black-and-white film negatives (35mm)
        All frames are from the G-Warren Grove; 56GT Firehouse Halloween party; Frame 0, Martha Kremer and sons; Frame 3, Olga? - Route 539; Frames 31 & 32, Cleaning up after the party; Frames 33-36, Returning the fire trucks to the fire house; Frame 37, John Budd of Warren Grove.
      - Warren Grove firehouse supper; Woods walk with Jack Cervetto and John Budd, Warren Grove, New Jersey, October 22, 1983 to October 28, 1983, AFC 1991/023: 217302-09; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-BNR-217302-09; 37 black-and-white film negatives (35mm); Thomas DeBlasio Carroll
        Slides from 1 to 29 are from the G-Warren Grove; 56GT firehouse supper and show various participants; Frames 1 & 2, The table in one room, laden with food prepared by the Ladies's Auxiliary; Frames 3-6, The tables in the firehouse and the line to the food table Frames 3 & 4 show field worker Tom Carroll, Frame 4 shows fieldworker Mal O'Connor and Warren Grove resident, John Budd; Frames 7 & 8, Food table; Frames 9 & 10, Olga and friend preparing for the 50-50 raffle; Frame 11, Mal O'Connor, John Budd and Mary-Ann Thompson (I to r); Frame 12, Mary-Ann Thompson; Frame 16, Cleaning up in the kitchen, shows Olga at extreme left and Peggy Grasser at extreme right; Frame 18, Pearl Cervetto at center; Frame 20, Jenny Holloway at center, Laurie Lonergan, President of Ladies' Auxiliary, at right; Frame 26, Bill Smith, Michael Smith, Mal O'Connor, John Budd, Mary Ann Thompson; Frame 27 & 28, Pearl Cervetto; Frame 29, The Ladies' Auxilliary; The following slides are from a woods walk with Jack Cervetto and John Budd. G-Warren Grove; 56GT; Frame 30, Jack Cervetto and John Budd; Frames 31-34, Cut off cedar swamp belonging to Jack Cervetto and once owned by Gerber who had bought it from the Jersey Proprieters; Frame 35, Old sawmill in Warren Grove; Frames 36-38, Jack Cervetto's cedar poles
      - Apple pressing for cider, Port Republic, New Jersey, October 9, 1983, AFC 1991/023: 217771-01; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-BNR-217771-01; 38 black-and-white film negatives (35mm)
        Index data: Pressing apples, G-Port Republic: 13GT The Sinton family and friends.
    - Field photography on color slide film
      - C log (color photo log), Nora Jane Rubinstein; 16 manuscript pages (8.5 x 14 inch or smaller) (Box-folder 16/152)
      - Guided tour of "neighborhood" of Steve Soviczki, Atsion, New Jersey, October 10, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CNR-001; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-CNR-001; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        G-Atsion; 22GT 1, old brick house on Jackson Road, near historic community of Flyatt, on the grounds of the old "Braddock" farm; 2, 3, Old Crain homestead - now owned by John Henry Clay Jennings (near Oak Shade /Jackson Rd and G-Indian Mills Road; 22GT or G-; 25GT and near the Tumble Inn corner); 4, 5, 6, 7, Suburban development near Crain homestead G-Barton Lukes: 25GT development; 8, Elementary school playground at G-Indian Mills; 25GT; 9, 10, G-Indian Mills; 25GT Methodist Church; 11, Steve Soviczki at Tabernacle cemetery at ancestral Crain grave stone; 12, Tabernacle cemetery (Haines grave stone); 13, Tabernacle cemetery - Grave of Indian Ann - last of the Delaware Indians to live in the area; 14, Tabernacle cemetery; 15, 16, old cranberry house, G-Johnstown-Stokes Road: 25GT or G-; 22GT near Route 206; 17, 18, Farm Labor Transport Bus - at Cranberry House above in Johnstown. G-Shamong-22-Tabernacle-25GT; 19, 20, Soviczki home, G-Atsion; 22GT
      - Warren Grove, Fire houses Supper, Warren Grove, New Jersey, October 22, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CNR-002; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-CNR-002; 22 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        Fire house supper G-Warren Grove: 56;GT; 1, Warren Grove residents; 2, Manahawkin residents originally from North Jersey and Pennsylvania); 3, Unidentified participants; 4, Michael Smith, Warren Grove; 5, Mal O'Connor - Folk life Project Fieldworker; 6, 7, 8, Participants; 9, 10, 11, 13, Raffle Drawing; 12, Participants; 13, 14, 15, 16, Mal O'Connor winning door prize; 17, Mal at the table with .John Budd, Mal, Michael Smith, and Bill Smith (counter-clockwise from right), Warren Grove; 18, Raffle winner; 19, 20, Preparing for the raffle; 21, Door prize; 22, Saying good-night.
      - Logging; Wandering, Waterford, New Jersey, Firehouse supper, Warren Grove, New Jersey, October 19, 1983 to October 22, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CNR-003; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-CNR-003; 27 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-7, Logging Operation, Fiusnak Family, Chew Road, G-Waterford; 32GT; 8, Sue Samuelson, Project Headquarters, G-Lebanon State Forest; 27 GT; 9; Sue Samuelson and Alan Jabbour, Pakim Pond, G-Lebanon State Forest.; 27GT; 10, 11, Pakim Pond, Lebanon State Forest; 12, Sue Samuelson on nature trail, Lebanon State Forest; 13, Beaver dam, Lebanon State Forest; 14, 15, Trail markers, Lebanon State Forest; 16, Pine sap on injured tree, Lebanon State Forest. 17-27; Fire House Supper, G-Warren Grove; 56GT. Participants include Mary Budd, Mary Ann Thompson, John Budd, Mal O'Connor, Bill Smith, Tom Carroll, Jack Cervetto, Jr., Pat Mirth, Olga ?, Jack Cervetto, Sr., Pearl Cervetto and many others.
      - Woods walk in Lebanon State Forest, New Jersey; Woods walk with Jack Cervetto and John Budd, October 26, 1983 to October 28, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CNR-004; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-CNR-004; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        Woods walk in G-Lebanon State Forest; 27GT; 01 -02, Fungus-like growth on dead tree; 03-04, Chestnut huils (?) in Lebanon State Forest Woods walk with Jack Cervetto G-Warren Grove; 56GT; 05-06, Plain branch, the "slough" dividing Jack's island from the surrounding land. Cedar growth across the slough will be cut off this year if it freezes over; 07, (left to right) John Budd and Jack Cervetto at slough; 08, (left to right) Jack Cervetto and John Budd walking away from slough; 09, Jack Cervetto and John Budd in Jack's 1941 Jeep; 10, Jack's land bought from Gerber bought from Jersey Proprieters. Planned as a cranberry bog but remains cut off cedar swamp; 11, Bridge over sluice gate for bog; 12, Deer track at bog dam; 13-16, Old saw mill and slave cabins in Warren Grove off AT&T right of way; 17, Jack's cedar poles; 18, Jack's log lifter; 19, Jack and John in the jeep; 20, Jack, John and Pearl Cervetto at Papoose Branch
      - Warren Grove Firehouse Halloween party, Warren Grove, New Jersey, October 29, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CNR-005; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-CNR-005; 23 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-20: Children at G-Warren Grove; 56GT Fire house halloween party; Frames 6, 9, 16-23, Woman in Angel costume is President of the Ladies Auxiliary, Laurie Lonergan (?); Frame 8, Richie Grasser (blue plaid shirt); Frame 9, Peggy Grasser (long blue dress)
      - Warren Grove Fire House Halloween party, Warren Grove, New Jersey, October 29, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CNR-006; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-CNR-006; 17 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        G-Warren Grove; 56GT fire house Halloween party; Frames 1 to 14, Halloween Party at Warren Grove; Frame 1, Woman in blue dress is Peggy Grasser, in blue Jacket, Lucille of Lucille's luncheonette in town; Frame 5, Peggy Grasser; Frame 10, Girl with "skunk"; Frame 11; Guess how many candy corns in the jar, and win it; Frame 12: Fireman's boots; Frames 15-17, Returning the trucks to the firehouse after the party
      - Woods walk; Benefit for the Old Stone Store in Manahawkin, New Jersey, October 28, 1983 to October 29, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CNR-007; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-CNR-007; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1, John Budd, and Jack and Pearl Cervetto near G-Papoose; 56GT settlement; 2, Origin al Indian clam sheell mound near Indian settlement; 3, Wire grass near Indian settlement; 4, Woodpecker eaten tree (?); 5, Indian pipes; 6, Sweet fern- "woodjin's enemy" 7: Pearl and Jack Cervetto near home of R. Blanchard near G-Stevenson Road; 56GT; 8; Dock at Blanchard house; 9 and 10, Blanchard house; 11, View from G-Bear Swamp Hill; 56GT; 12, Pearl, Jack and John at Bear Swamp Hill; 13 and 14, Near duck breeding ground - target practice; 15, Pig on G-Beaver Dam Road; 56GT in Warren Grove; 16, Pine Barrens Gentian on Braver Dam Rd.; 17 and 18, Ed Hazelton, Jack Cervetto and John Budd (left to right); 19 and 20: Old Stone Store in G-Manahawkin; 56GT; 20, Jack Cervetto is bending over the table preparing for the raffle and John Budd is standing to --the right of the door
      - Benefit at the Old Stone Store in Manahawkin, New Jersey, October 29, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CNR-008; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-CNR-008; 3 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        Elenefit for Old Stone Store in G-Manahawkin; 56GT; Frames 1-3, Old Stone Store; Frame 1, John Budd at window, Ed Hazelton at door, Jack Cervetto in hunting cap; Frame 2, Ed Hazelton in blue jacket; Frame 3, Jack Cervetto in hunting Jacket
      - Woods walk with John Budd near Warren Grove, New Jersey, November 5, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CNR-009; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-CNR-009; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        Woods walk near G-Warren Grove; 56GT; Frames 1-12, From the Warren Grove/Reevestown cemetery; 11, John Budd is in the background; Frame 13-16, Cliff Oakley's house, Wells Mills; 13, Old mill stone; 14, View from porch to mill pond; 15-16, Mill pond; Frame 17, Tilden Eslow carriage house; 18 & 19, Roof of Tilden Eslow carriage house; 20, Tilden Eslow house
      - Woods walk with John Budd near Warren Grove, New Jersey, November 5, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CNR-010; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-CNR-010; 7 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        Tilden Eslow house, G-Brookvilie; 56GT; All frames from the Eslow house; Frame 4 is of one of the hand hewn interior beams; 6 is of the front of the house; 7, is a nearby street sign indicating E. Delaware Ave.
      - Woods walk at Harrisville and Martha Furnace, Harrisville, New Jersey, November 5, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CNR-011; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-CNR-011; 16 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        G-HarrisvllIe; 15GT ruins; Frame 1, Harrisville water spring fed; 2-5, Harrisville ruins; 4, The red section is part of the old chimney Imported, hand planted trees near Harrisville; 6, Grape vine choked cedar tree; 7, Apple tree; 8 & 9, Trees, unknown type at Harrisville; Frames 10-16, G-Martha Furnace; 15GT; 10, John Budd and Jack Cervetto (I to r); 11, Old foundation at Martha; 12 & 13, Deer stand at Martha; 14, 01d settlement at Martha; 15, Lightening struck tree; 16, Hollowed out tree base
      - Wandering around and cider pressing at the Sinton's, Port Republic, New Jersey, October 9, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CNR-012; Nora Jane Rubinstein; PFP-83-CNR-012; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)